Contact

6016850484 (Mobile) alijenkinsrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/msalirenee (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Problem Solving
Medical Education

Certifications
NRP

Alison Jenkins

Registered Nurse Seeking employment in utilization review or work from home jobs.

Richmond, Texas

Summary

I am a honor graduate of Meridian Community College with an associate degree in nursing. I graduated in 2015 from Jones County Junior College with a certificate as a cosmetologist. I am presently enrolled in college to obtain my BSN. I will graduate in July 2020 at Mississippi University for Women with my BSN. I have five years of NICU level II experience including floating to other areas such as newborn nursery, postpartum/mother-baby, and pediatrics.

Experience

Seeking employment
Registered Nurse
April 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months)
Jackson, MS

utilization review, data entry, auditing

HCA Gulf Coast Division
Registered Nurse
January 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

NICU LEVEL II, NEWBORN NURSERY- TOTAL INFANT CARE:
ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/
NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2
SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL
CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT
MEASURES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/EPISODES PER
NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION.

Woman's Hospital
TRAVEL RN LEVEL II NICU/NEWBORN NURSERY
August 2016 - December 2016 (5 months)
Houston, Texas Area

TOTAL INFANT CARE: ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2 SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT MEASURES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/EPISODES PER NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION.

CHI SAINT LUKE SUGAR LAND, TX TRAVEL RN LEVEL II NICU June 2016 - September 2016 (4 months) SUGAR LAND, TX

TOTAL INFANT CARE: ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2 SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT MEASURES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/ EPISODES PER NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION.

MERIT HEALTH WESLEY STAFF RN LEVEL III NICU August 2015 - April 2016 (9 months) Hattiesburg, Mississippi Area

TOTAL INFANT CARE: ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2 SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT MEASURES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/EPISODES PER NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION. FLOAT TO POSTPARTUM/PEDIATRICS AS NEEDED WITH TOTAL PATIENT CARE PROVIDED.

NA
GAP IN EMPLOYMENT
April 2011 - August 2015 (4 years 5 months)
VALDOSTA, GEORGIA

South Georgia Medical Center STAFF RN LEVEL II NICU March 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 2 months) VALDOSTA, GEORGIA TOTAL INFANT CARE: ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2 SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT MEASURES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/ EPISODES PER NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION.

Jeff Anderson Regional Medical Center RN LEVEL II NICU October 2009 - February 2010 (5 months) MERIDIAN, MS

TOTAL INFANT CARE: ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2 SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT MEASURES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/ EPISODES PER NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION.

Bayfront Health St. Petersburg STAFF RN LEVEL II NICU March 2008 - July 2009 (1 year 5 months) Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

TOTAL INFANT CARE: ASSESSMENTS, MEDICATIONS, IV FLUIDS, LAB DRAWS, TPN, IM/PO/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, CARDIAC MONITORS, O2 SATURATION MONITORS, INFANT BATHS, INFANT BATHS, UMBILICAL CORD CARE, BOTTLE FEEDING WITH PACING AND SUPPORT MEASURES, VENTILATION/ET TUBE MONITORING, HELP WITH UVC/UAC LINES, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY CHANGES/EPISODES PER NURSING PROTOCOL, AND PARENTAL EDUCATION.

RUSH FOUNDATION HOSPITAL
Staff RN 4 NORTH- MED/SURG/ORTHOPEDICS/ONCOLOGY
August 2007 - February 2008 (7 months)
MERIDIAN, MS

TOTAL PATIENT CARE: MED/SURG, ONCOLOGY, ORTHOPEDICS-ASSESSMENTS, NEURO CHECKS, VITAL SIGNS, TRACTION PLACEMENT AND CONTINUOUS MONITORING, MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, NG/OG PLACEMENT PER ORDERS, IM/PO/SC/NG/OG MEDICATION ADMINISTRATION, IV FLUID START WITH MAINTENANCE, LAB DRAWS, ASSESSING PAIN STATUS AND NEURO CHECKS EVERY HOUR/2

HOURS, NOTIFYING PHYSICIAN OF ANY ABNORMAL SYMPTOMS/ LABS/PROBLEMS PER NURSING PROTOCOL, PATIENT AND FAMILY EDUCATION.

Education

Mississippi University for Women

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2019 - 2020)

Jones County Junior College
Associate's degree, Cosmetology, Barber/Styling, and Nail
Instructor · (2015 - 2017)

Meridian Community College
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2003 - 2007)